[
  
  
      {
        "question": "What is the weather like?",
        "choice1": "che tempo fa ?",
        "choice2": "fa bell tempo",
        "choice3": "fa fresco",
        "choice4": "lampeggia",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "it's nice out",
        "choice1": "fa freddo",
        "choice2": "fa bell tempo",
        "choice3": "fa caldo",
        "choice4": "tira vento",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "it's ok out",
        "choice1": "gradi",
        "choice2": "fa bell tempo",
        "choice3": "ne`, bello ne`,brutto",
        "choice4": "lampeggia",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "bad weather",
        "choice1": "tira vento",
        "choice2": "fa bell tempo",
        "choice3": "fa freddo",
        "choice4": "fa brutto tempo",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "it is sunny",
        "choice1": "c` e` il sole",
        "choice2": "Tuono",
        "choice3": "gradi",
        "choice4": "nevica",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "it's cool",
        "choice1": "nevica",
        "choice2": "fa fresco",
        "choice3": "fa caldo",
        "choice4": "fa freddo",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "it's cold",
        "choice1": "nevica",
        "choice2": "piove",
        "choice3": "fa freddo",
        "choice4": "Tuono",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "it's warm/hot",
        "choice1": "Tuono",
        "choice2": "nevica",
        "choice3": "fa freddo",
        "choice4": "fa caldo",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "it's windy",
        "choice1": "tira vento",
        "choice2": "ne`, bello ne`,brutto",
        "choice3": "fa fresco",
        "choice4": "Tuono",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "it's windy",
        "choice1": "fa fresco",
        "choice2": "c` e` vento",
        "choice3": "nevica",
        "choice4": "tira vento",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "lightning",
        "choice1": "piove",
        "choice2": "nevica",
        "choice3": "lampeggia",
        "choice4": "Tuono",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "it's foggy",
        "choice1": "ne`, bello ne`,brutto",
        "choice2": "fa fresco",
        "choice3": "Tuono",
        "choice4": "E` afoso",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "it's snowing",
        "choice1": "nevica",
        "choice2": "gradi",
        "choice3": "fa caldo",
        "choice4": "piove",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "it's cloudy",
        "choice1": "fa fresco",
        "choice2": "E` nuvoloso",
        "choice3": "ne`, bello ne`,brutto",
        "choice4": "piove",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "it thunders",
        "choice1": "nevica",
        "choice2": "lampeggia",
        "choice3": "Tuono",
        "choice4": "E` nuvoloso",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "it's raining",
        "choice1": "fa caldo",
        "choice2": "nevica",
        "choice3": "gradi",
        "choice4": "piove",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "degrees",
        "choice1": "gradi",
        "choice2": "fa bell tempo",
        "choice3": "lampeggia",
        "choice4": "tira vento",
        "answer": 1
      }
]
